SYMPATHY
is everything ok
Gi Joon was coming.
Nam Gi Joon?
How many memories through this name!
So he's still alive, huh?
But he asked something strange.
Does he need to know something?
about Gi Seok's death.
Considering how his brother died,
Is this a strange question?
It seems normal to me.
That's why I want to ask you.
Is there anything I should know about Gi Seok's death?
This is actually what I wanted to ask you.
I heard Mr. Nam recently
talked about plans to leave the company,
which you lead.
This must have upset you quite a bit.
Well, you know how curious I am.
Find out if it really was that youngster.
Yes, sir.
WITHOUT MERCY
Nam Gi Seok was the second person
in the management of "Chuvun".
He helped legitimize the business.
He was in charge
corporate gallery "Chuvun",
where the company's money was laundered.
Let's look a little further into the past.
Gangs "Chuwoon" and "Bonsan" arose,
when the "Bomyeongdong" gang, which once
controlled Seoul, split in half.
That gang was led by this man
head O.
His first supervisors, Lee Choo Woon
and Gu Bong San, staged a coup.
The incident that provoked the coup,
was the death of his son, named Oh Son Won.
It's strangely similar
on the recent case of Nam Gi-seok.
So you want to say
that the death of Nam Gi Seok, the heir,
lead to a new war?
Are you exaggerating?
Absolutely not.
Then dozens of people died
in gangster leggings in the middle of Seoul
in just five months
before the presidential elections.
You know how many people
fired then from law enforcement structures?
Did those young men act alone in Nam's case?
According to the police report, yes.
Forget about the report. Do we know that for sure?
Probably...
Leave the room.
Sorry?
Everyone away.
No, you stay.
You have reached the position of special agent,
and they treat you like a stranger.
And at home you are like an invisible person.
I saw how you
put out from the funeral yesterday.
Are you still following me?
Am I watching?
Do not flatter yourself.
I was at the funeral too.
It seemed that Mr. Lee
not the same as before.
When your father retires,
maybe you will leave the prosecutor's office
and will you move to Chuvun as a lawyer?
I never thought about it.
Really?
And here everyone is of the same opinion.
Let's be honest with each other.
If nothing changes,
you will never reach a higher position.
But also "Chuvun Group"
will not accept you am i right
What do you mean by that?
I'm giving you a chance.
chance to choose
whose side are you on, and get up.
I want you to
handled Nam Gi-seok's case.
where are you
Bro, just do all that,
what will he say, okay?
Everything is fine with him now.
So tell me.
Who tipped you off?
OK.
Devil.
you won
Have you heard about "Cemetery"?
Blyaha, you are old.
There is a chat called "Cemetery".
It's so fugitives like me
they did dirty work for money.
And that time
a huge deal has appeared.
No one has offered so much money before.
I swear, I didn't know anything.
I was told where to go and whom to kill.
And I didn't care who he was.
Do you understand?
Is that all?
Devil.
The "Cemetery" sent me a lawyer.
Ask her yourself.
I will call her here.
STATEMENT
CHUNG YU CHANG
Well done do you see
I told you that you can.
Finally.
And let me explain.
Don't cheat and don't do anything.
In such situations
follow the advice of an expert. Clear?
Hold on, lady.
Pope.
Aha.
Yes, he just signed the statement.
I don't think there will be any problems.
Children are children.
They behave decently in custody.
Yes.
Either way, transfer the rest of the money now.
He will be next week
in the center of serving sentences.
You can end it there.
Yes.
Okay, I'll hang up.
Good.
And who are you?
I am the older brother
Nam Gi Seok, the guy who was killed.
Man are you out of your mind?
You understand where we are, right?
We are near the police station, and I am a lawyer.
do you really think
that you can threaten or blackmail me?
And what?
Is there anything to blackmail?
You know about "Cemetery", right?
Okay, I'll say it all.
This "Cemetery"...
It's like food delivery apps -
communication between suppliers and couriers,
but connects customers
with impersonators.
Do something!
Shut up!
I screwed up.
Someone should go to jail for me.
Mom's in a month
pre-election check! Find someone!
Yes, I'm already doing it.
Of course. OK.
Girls, attention!
"I need a boyfriend
who will sit for the murder of a young woman."
We publish.
I will explain everything now.
Some A committed a crime,
but does not want to go to prison.
B is ready to be a front person for money.
A is demand, and B is supply.
"Cemetery" connects them.
Demand is always high,
but there is a problem with the offer.
But the "Cemetery" is full of runaway children,
who have not yet served in the army.
Ahoy! Post at the "Cemetery".
- "Cemetery"?
- Always.
- What is there?
- Grandpa.
There is a necessary offer!
OK.
Prison is evasion
from the army plus money.
attempted rape
reduced to indecent behavior.
The foundation has just been laid,
An expert like me finishes the job
legally
That's all I know.
i'm just human
which periodically provides
legal services for the company.
I swear
If you do not believe, ask them yourself.
Seriously.
NCLEAN
CEO SIM SONG WON
Do you remember that fortune teller? She was right.
She said that this month to me
good luck And I have an international contract.
Wow, that's gorgeous.
This is already a world level.
Congratulations, boss.
Congratulations too soon, fool. We are just getting started.
Any news from the lawyer?
She said she already took care of everything.
Do you see? Maybe it's not easy with her,
but she does what it takes.
NCLEAN
Who came so late?
I need to talk to Mr. Sim
and change the host.
- It won't work.
- You are right.
Sir, can I help you with something?
In general, we are closed...
Detain him.
Excuse me, sir.
We are already closed.
May I ask what brought you here?
Call me Sim Song Won.
So you came to see Mr. Sim.
If I may, I ask
Are you aware of our activities?
So you know everything, right?
What's going on?
Take him out.
Expose it from here.
Devil!
What does the Chuvun company say? Still nothing?
Nothing. They seem to have concluded
that it was done by minors.
But purely for safety
cover that "Cemetery" for a certain time.
I listen.
OFFICE RECEPTION
What is it?
Sim Song Wone.
What is it? What the hell? Who is speaking?
This is me, Nam Gi Joon.
You know why I'm calling, right?
I will wait.
How could I forget the most important person?
That's a bitch.
Hey, how many guys are in the office right now?
Die!
Devil!
Mr. Director.
Oh, look who's here!
Owwa, Gijun, friend. Long time no see.
Agov.
Stupid asshole. Get up, doubna!
Well, because
Nice to meet you, Director Name.
No, not like that.
What's your name now?
Mr. Nam Gi Joon?
Gi Jun.
Even if I seem very important
nothing has changed since you disappeared.
They tell me: "Clean up", and I clean up.
They say: "Cover", - I cover.
You yourself know how it works.
I'm just following orders.
So you knew Gi Seok was a target.
Who says so? The hatchlings!
I was just following orders as usual.
I didn't know. I didn't know anything.
At least at first.
But I already took the money. What could I do?
That is...
I couldn't do anything.
Grandfather, legs.
I'm not a psycho. If I knew…
I wouldn't do that.
Did you say everything?
Listen, Gi Joon.
That is, Mr. Name. Let's think logically.
Why do you think I sent those little ones?
If the target is Nam Gi Seok,
I would send a professional.
God, I can't believe he's dead.
Who was it?
What?
I ask who is it?
Gi Jun, you know
trust is the main thing in this business.
If word spreads,
that I betrayed the client, my business then…
And if I tell you
you will have problems too.
I will decide this myself.
Gu Jun Mo.
Son of Goo Bong San, the company's president.
He ordered the murder.
So what?
Are you going to fight Bonsan alone?
Really?
Are you sure it was Jun Mo?
Yes. Confident.
I will prepare everyone.
Goo Bong San.
I will go to him first.
Yes, sir.
Don't you think it's time to choose a side?
Lee Choo Woon will kill us, no other way.
Maybe it's time to leave business forever
from "Chuwoon" and merge with "Bonsan"...
shut up You're already giving me a headache.
You think I'm paying you to chat?
I'm trying to think, so shut up.
Boss, this is Mr. Kim from Bonsan Group.
Say I'm not there.
Did Gi Joon come here yesterday?
don't ask me
Do I have to report every little thing to you?
Gi Seok's order…
Did Mr. Gu personally hire you for this?
Yes. To hell with it!
I'm already sneezing.
Clean up your own shit.
Damn, I'm fed up already.
come out
You damn bastard.
Do you not understand what is happening?
Well, because
No need to swear like that.
How much does Gi Joon know?
And don't make a fool of me here, damn it.
Does Gi Joong know that Gu Joong Mo hired you?
What did you expect?
It's about Nam Gi Joon, okay?
Do you think he gave me a choice?
Is that all you can say, you bastard?
What about you yourself?
Would you go up against Nam Gi Joon?
Devil.
I'll kill that damn fortune teller.
This is such a surprise.
I can't believe you called me first.
How long ago did we start drinking together here?
But you didn't just call me for that.
Tell me.
Thanks to which we have
can you meet like this?
Thanks to the rule,
which we agreed after the death of Mr. O.
That's right.
"Whoever attacks the other side,
he must pay for it."
Whoever causes a mess must pay
or your life,
or something equivalent.
For God's sake.
It's enough to talk about it,
let's get down to business.
Even if this is your son,
there can be no exceptions.
always
What the hell are you talking about?
you know what i thought
just found out about Gi Seok?
I thought: "Let's not attack.
That would be an accident.
Accident at the hands of minors."
didn't you hear me
What are you doing?
Your son, Jun Mo, hired Sim Song Won.
That's why Gi Joon
crushed by NClean yesterday.
You will have to
to answer for these words of yours.
You think I didn't check the facts?
now you understand
Why did I mention this rule?
Yes, I understand.
I hope you haven't forgotten
why did this rule come about in the first place.
If only Nam Gi Joon
didn't screw it up 11 years ago
there would be no need for this damn rule.
what you just said
will be a problem
is it true or not.
How dare you threaten my son's life?
Just touch Jun Mo,
do you think I'll keep quiet?
Rightly.
Because you know the truth
now you must act.
That is, you have no choice.
Or force your son to follow the rules,
or you must fight me.
But know, Gu,
that's not why I called you
to discuss it.
Like I said, Gi Joon crushed NClean.
Haven't you figured it out yet?
Don't understand what awaits you?
- Sir
- Are they inside?
Let me ask one last time.
You somehow
involved in Gi Seok's death?
Nam Gi Joon!
Just answer.
You bastard!
Gi Jun.
The death of your brother is not your only concern.
This is just as bad for Chuvun.
I will take care of it.
Does this mean
that you will follow the rule?
You are no longer working with us.
And following the rules is not your business.
But you'll stick to it, right?
OK.
We will figure it out
with Sim Sung-won and the little ones.
Don't interfere.
There is no need for this.
I already know…
who was behind it.
These are not your instructions
right?
I think not.
In that case
you can do nothing.
Just watch.
Let me make amends to Jun Mo.
Just say what you want.
Casino? My duty free shops?
Or something else?
You have to do something.
You can't let Gi Joon
destroy everything
And what should I do? Kill him?
If Jun Mo dies…
this relationship is over.
Mark my words.
This will be our last meeting over a drink.
take away
Because if you start building a hotel now,
you won't live to see it open.
So why build it?
Take better mine.
Hotel "De'Cro".
I will give it to you.
Sir…
Greetings, sir.
Was it really you?
What?
Did you do that?
Answer!
how to answer
when i don't know what are you talking about?
Nam Gi Seok.
Did you do that?
That's shit!
Yes.
I did it.
And what?
"So what?"
You're a jerk!
Did you miss Cha?
Did you also eliminate Nam? Why?
That scumbag humiliated me
in front of my people.
And that's it?
This is not the first time you have been humiliated.
You live like this all your life.
It doesn't matter, one more or less?
Do you see?
Even my own father
exposes me to everyone
worthless piece of shit!
That's why I try
prove your worth!
Why prove something?
If you are even unworthy,
is that why you are not my son?
Jun Mo.
Don't you understand why I'm so angry?
So you don't get killed by Nam Gi Joon,
don't do anything without asking me.
Of course?
Careful, Chi Ho. Move your hips.
Bam! One, two.
Bam! Try it.
Did you come to tell the ball?
We have daytime classes only for children.
Gi Jun.
I was at the funeral.
I thought I had to at least
to say goodbye to Gi Seok.
But I didn't linger, because
didn't want to face those scumbags.
Someone ordered Gi Suk, right?
And you know who that is, huh?
Gi Seok used to visit me before that.
Did he say something?
No, almost nothing.
But I saw everything.
Because something was wrong.
So now
I need a bull like my old one.
Of course. Good.
To make it,
it takes some time so…
Here, take this first.
It's not just anyone, we're talking about Mr. Nam.
If you don't mind it,
then our people will not understand you.
You suggest to start
a war with "Bonsan" or something?
- We won't win anything.
- If you create such a precedent...
Ahoy!
I'm tired
Greetings.
What happened?
what are you doing here
I am with Mr. President.
How is he?
OK. What is the matter?
Tell me better.
I say, tell me.
I already said, didn't I?
After the fight with Gu Jun Mo…
He was killed that evening.
I understand what we have been waiting for
the end of the funeral
but it's time for Mr. Chairman to do something.
He knows that it was Gu Jun Mo.
What?
Our job is to carry out the boss's decision.
So he doesn't want to do anything?
And you don't mind?
Agov.
don't forget
who are you here
Aha.
I know my place.
You probably like it.
Because you will soon take over Gi Seok's position.
Mr. Choi.
How disgusting to contemplate.
I teach him manners.
But you shouldn't beat him,
like it's a gang showdown.
This is the company's job,
and it does not concern you.
And yet, Mr. Choi.
do you really think
that you won't win anything, only lose?
These are my affairs.
Do not interfere.
The company wants to forget about all this.
Follow this decision.
Of course.
Someone already told me that.
We just have to follow the boss's decision.
But I never
I will not respect such a person as my boss.
It's not just your business.
She is mine too.
Grandpa, I'm starving.
Name is Gu Jun Mo.
Manager of the company "Bonsan",
director of the De'Cro hotel.
The car is a white Maserati Ghibli.
Number plate 26D 7123.
We publish.
GU JUNG MO
DIRECTOR OF DE'CRO HOTEL
Let me know if you see him.
GU JUNG MO
DIRECTOR OF "DE'CRO"
- Oh, look.
- What is there?
It's not him. Let's look further.
- EVERYDAY
- IDENTICAL
CEMETERY MANAGER
THE SEARCH FOR GU JUNG MO
30 MILLION WON
CHEONDAM, APKUJEON
The number is different!
They are already trading.
Does he go to church?
26D 7123
grandfather
Curse.
Here, Gu Jun Mo has been found!
Ah, we found him!
Really?
Sir.
There is a location.
DE'CRO HOTEL
WITHOUT MERCY
I knew he would do something like that someday.
Is this really Jun Mo?
are you sure
Yes, sure.
Gu Joon Mo, Director of Bonsan.
He hired NClean,
to kill Nam Gi-seok.
I knew he would do something like that someday.
Does Gi Joon know about this?
Yes, it already crushed NClean.
but sir
this is probably only the beginning, not the end.
11-year-old rule
set when Nam Gi Joon left.
Now that he's back,
time to establish a new rule.
That is?
I want to say,
what is possible according to the old rule
make Gu Jun Mo pay with his life,
or a deal can be made
with Mr. Gu and forget about all this,
or maybe
like 11 years ago
you can turn everything around
from head to toe and take everything for yourself.
Whatever you decide, everything depends
not from Nam Gi Joon or Goo Bong San.
Everything depends on you, sir.
Remember this.
You didn't have a choice before.
But now everything depends on your decision.
Do you understand me?
REQUEST FOR A SEARCH WARRANT
SUSPECT: GU BON SUN
PROSECUTOR: LEE GIM SONG
SUSPECT: LEE CHOO WUN
Translation of subtitles: Olga Tsiatska